amarchitrakatha.com 2012-09-29

# Privacy Policy | Amar Chitra Katha: Indian Stories for Children - Books, Comics, DVDs and more

Amar Chitra Katha Pvt. Ltd. respects your privacy. This privacy policy provides a clear description of the data gathered and used by us. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies to information collected at our websites [www.ack-media.com](http://www.ack-media.com/ "www.ack-media.com"), [www.amarchitrakatha.com](http://www.amarchitrakatha.com/ "www.amarchitrakatha.com") and [www.tinkleonline.com](http://www.tinkleonline.com/ "www.tinkleonline.com"). By accessing the services provided by Amar Chitra Katha Pvt. Ltd. you agree to the collection and use of your data by Amar Chitra Katha Pvt. Ltd. in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

### Part I. Information Collection 

Amar Chitra Katha Pvt. Ltd. will collect information through our Web site at several points. We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from a * web server cookie stored on your hard drive * an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use * the domain server through which you access our service * the type of computer you're using * the type of web browser you're using We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: * name including first and last name * alternate email address * mobile phone number and contact details * ZIP/Postal code * demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned); * preferences and interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on); * financial information (like account or credit card numbers); and * opinions of features on our websites. We may also collect the following information: * about the pages you visit/access * the links you click on our site * the number of times you access the page You can terminate your account at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

### Part II. Information Usage

We use your personal information to: * help us provide personalized features * tailor our sites to your interest * to get in touch with you when necessary * to provide the services requested by you * to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy We use contact information internally to: * direct our efforts for product improvement * contact you as a survey respondent * notify you if you win any contest; and * send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers Generally, we use anonymous traffic information to: * remind us of who you are in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service from both an advertising and an editorial perspective; * recognize your access privileges to our Web sites * track your entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests to indicate a player's progress through the promotion and to track entries, submissions, and status in prize drawings * make sure that you don't see the same ad repeatedly * help diagnose problems with our server * administer our Web sites * track your session so that we can understand better how people use our sites.

### Part III. Access to Information

We will not use your financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you. We do not rent, sell or share your personal information and we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless: * we have your permission * to provide products or services you've requested * to help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of [www.amarchitrakatha.com](http://www.amarchitrakatha.com/ "www.amarchitrakatha.com") 's terms of use or to defend against legal claims; * special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure. We share your information with advertisers on an aggregate basis only.

### Part IV. Data Storage and Security

To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, we have in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures. For example, our servers are accessible only to authorized personnel and that your information is shared with respective personnel on need to know basis to complete the transaction and to provide the services requested by you. Although we will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

### Part V. Problem Resolution 

To correct or update any information you have provided, our sites allow you to do it online. In the event of loss of access details you can use any of the following options: * send an e-mail to [contact@ack-media.com](mailto:contact@ack-media.com) * call us at +91 (22) 66296999 

### Part VI. Policy Updates

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site.
